Welcome to the wine competition.
Next up is Valley Breeze Group's winemaker
Ye Xiaowei, presenting
Eucalyptus Leaf.
Judges, please have a taste.
Although Ms. Ye is new to winemaking,
she is very likely
a dark horse in this competition.
It seems the judges
are very satisfied with Eucalyptus Leaf.
Let's welcome
the winemaker,
Ye Xiaowei!
Are you ready?
Go ahead.
Go and embrace
the glory that belongs to you.
Here I go.
I'll wait for you right here.
I once thought
the dark night of my life
had finally seen the dawn.
Success.
Love.
Family.
I had everything I ever longed for.
Ms. Ye,
as for your inspiration for Eucalyptus Leaf,
would you mind sharing it?
It was someone
who is very special to me.
We truly must thank this mysterious person
for inspiring you to craft this fine wine.
What's going on?
There's something wrong with this wine!
There must be!
Ye Xiaowei!
It's her!
It's Ye Xiaowei!
Ms. Ye,
we suspect a problem with your wine.
Please cooperate with our investigation.
It wasn't me!
Little did I know,
this light was just an illusion,
fading in an instant.
Cheng An!
Cheng An...
Give me a child.
Wanmei.
I want a child who can inherit the Cheng family.
Go and embrace
the glory that belongs to you.
I'll wait for you right here.
Good morning, Grandma.
You really have no manners.
As expected from a bastard
with no upbringing.
Aunt, with your candid personality,
you must have learned a lot of manners.
I wonder which teacher taught you.
Maybe you could introduce them to me,
a bastard with no upbringing.
What did you say?
I'm complimenting you, Aunt.
You don't sweat the small stuff,
and you speak without a filter.
Of course, I need to learn from you.
Mom!
Look at her!
She dares to badmouth me right to your face.
Who knows how she badmouths us in private.
Or how she badmouths you!
Eat your food.
You need to rein in that temper of yours.
Mom,
I'm done eating.
I still have work at the company.
I'll be going now.
Go ahead.
Remember what I told you. These days,
don't cause any trouble.
Keep your head down.
I've heard it a million times.
Don't worry, I'll be good.
Auntie Ying.
Yes?
Since you have free time today,
teach Miss Sang Luo the house rules.
I don't want something like this
to happen ever again.
Yes, ma'am.
The Cheng family wakes up at 4:00 AM every day.
At 4:30 sharp, we pay respects to the old madam.
Morning exercise is at 5:00.
It must last at least two hours.
Keeping a good physical and mental state
represents the Cheng family's image.
Breakfast is at 7:00 sharp.
We wait for no one.
Are you done?
Call a car for me. I'm going out.
How unfortunate.
Miss Ruolin just took the last car.
What about the housekeeper's car?
That's the staff's utility vehicle.
I need to go out for groceries later
to prepare lunch for the old madam.
There's a bus stop nearby.
It's not far from here.
It's only a three-kilometer walk at most.
It seems that in the Cheng family,
Auntie Ying acts with complete impunity.
I don't understand what you mean, Miss.
Then Auntie Ying isn't a very smart servant.
As a dog,
when your master is lonely,
you can get whatever you want.
But once your master finds a new pet,
the old dog
will be sold off cheap and slaughtered.
Mind if I hitch a ride, Uncle?
Yes, I do.
If I say I mind,
Uncle, you can reject
someone on the same path as you.
But to reject
someone trying hard to keep pace with you
is just too cold.
I know
I'm very ordinary,
and plain.
I don't have a dazzling appearance,
but I really like you.
For the rest of my life,
I want to be on the same path as you.
And I'll work hard to keep pace with you.
You're not plain.
And you're not ordinary.
In my heart,
you are the most dazzling of all.
Learned that from a playbook.
To the bus stop.
I didn't expect
you to like such a modest car, Uncle.
I prefer cars like this.
Not too flashy on the outside,
but with exceptional performance.
Often, beneath a glamorous exterior,
lie disappointing flaws.
Ms. Sang,
sounds like you've done your research.
Just a little.
Just like how some positions
are filled by
people who aren't necessarily the best fit.
What do you mean?
Uncle, your proposal the other day was rejected, wasn't it?
Second Uncle's team
can't even make a decent financial report,
yet they easily overturned your proposal.
Grandma even said it was to save your pride.
Talk about playing favorites.
This is Valley Breeze's internal business.
It has nothing to do with you.
I thought I was here to solve this very problem.
Don't you want Valley Breeze
to be better?
We'll talk when you actually join the company.
That'll be soon, Uncle.
Thank you all for attending today's press conference.
At this year's wine competition,
Valley Breeze Group's winemaker Ye Xiaowei
added banned substances to her wine,
causing a judge acute kidney failure.
Valley Breeze takes full responsibility,
and will donate 5 million to the Kidney
Care Foundation for patient recovery.
Next, please welcome Cheng Feng, Chairman of Valley Breeze,
to make a formal statement regarding this incident.
First of all,
on behalf of the group,
I apologize to the judges who were hurt.
Since Valley Breeze was founded over 50 years ago,
we have never compromised on consumer health.
This time,
it was our failure in personnel management.
However, Ye Xiaowei's competition wine
was developed independently by her,
and has no connection to any Valley Breeze products.
We've ended all cooperation with Ms. Ye,
and are fully cooperating with the probe.
In fact,
the gatekeeper for every production step
is my wife,
and our chief winemaker, Lin Wanmei.
She has been immersed in this industry for over a decade.
Her standards for quality
are even stricter than those she sets for me.
That's why Evening Breeze, her creation,
won the championship at this competition
and topped sales in its first season.
It doesn't rely on luck,
but on standards.
Donating five million yuan
isn't just crisis PR.
It's Valley Breeze's responsibility to the industry.
We believe
a responsible brand
won't let the mistakes of others
shake its own foundation.
We spent so much money to hire you.
And you show me this garbage?
You can't even balance
the basic fruit and wine aromas.
And you want to enter the wine competition?
You'd be eliminated in the first round!
Right now,
red wines that can rival Evening Breeze
are truly rare.
Evening Breeze is my life's work.
In the current domestic wine market,
there is simply not a single wine
that can compare to it.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's just that...
relying solely on Evening Breeze
is hardly enough to sustain
Valley Breeze's market demand and status.
Do I need you to tell me that?
I heard
there's a mysterious winemaker in France,
Kista.
Recently, her wine appeared at the Fengtang Club.
I wonder if she intends to enter the domestic market.
If
we can manage
to get her as a consultant for our group,
perhaps in this wine competition,
we can take first place again.
It's just that...
Just what?
No one has ever seen Kista.
The Fengtang Club...
Money makes the world go round.
Do everything you can to get her info.
You must contact her in person.
Yes, Ms. Lin.
Throw this garbage out.
Yes.
Open the door.
Afraid of a misunderstanding?
Your older brother is gone.
What are you afraid of?
This matter
really shouldn't be discussed with the door open.
Do you want that position?
What position?
You know exactly what I mean.
Old Madam Cheng wants Cheng Yan in power.
But look at him.
If Valley Breeze is handed over to him,
Cheng Feng's life's work will be ruined.
You wouldn't want to see that, right?
I will support you.
As long as Valley Breeze is in our hands,
Cheng Feng's efforts won't be in vain.
It's better than
having someone else ruin it, right?
Don't you think?
Sister-in-law.
You want me to be your regent.
Cheng An.
Give me some time.
If there's nothing else,
you can leave now.
Don't make a fool of yourself here.
Some things are up to fate,
but it also takes human effort.
Cheng An.
Valley Breeze isn't yours,
nor is it mine.
But it can be ours.
A lowly bastard
has no right to covet my Cheng An.
So...
was this all your doing?
Delusions come with a price.
Let me teach you one last lesson today.
Rats
belong in the gutter.
The fame and fortune in the spotlight,
the people and the things...
you don't deserve any of them.
Cheng An...
Cheng An said
he got tired of playing with you long ago.
He also said
the sight of you makes him sick.
Go to hell!
Hurting again?
This is nothing.
They haven't tasted real pain yet.
Take a break if it hurts.
Don't push yourself.
Some wounds
must be paid back by yourself
to find redemption.
Alright.
What's next then?
What do you want to do?
I just joined the Cheng family.
I haven't gained their trust yet.
So I just need a chance to break the ice.
Boss.
Miss Sang.
Old Madam Cheng is downstairs.
Please enjoy.
Fengtang Club's food is always reliable.
They even use the finest Beluga caviar.
I went to Juehuang with a friend the other day.
They used sturgeon instead of Beluga.
How could anyone eat that?
Grandma.
What brings you here?
If I had known you were here,
I would've come with you.
Isn't this place
a private club?
Miss Sang is an old friend of our boss.
She's a lifetime member of Fengtang Club.
Let me introduce you.
This is my
newly found biological granddaughter.
Her name is Luoluo.
Luoluo,
come say hello to these two ladies.
Okay.
Nice to meet you.
Hello, ladies.
I'm Cheng Feng's daughter,
my name is Sang Luo.
For the 20-odd years I couldn't serve
the Cheng family, I feel deep regret.
Grandma's birthday happens to be next month,
I want to plan a grand celebration.
Manager Dong.
On the 18th of next month,
clear the schedule at Fengtang Club.
And that newly arrived batch
of Kista wine,
reserve all of it too.
I'll use it for Grandma's birthday.
Okay.
I'll arrange it right away.
I also hope you two ladies
will bring your friends and join us.
You mean that incredibly rare
wine by Master Kista?
I heard her wines
are always reserved by the elites.
Even I've only had the privilege of tasting it once.
You must all come then.
As for the wine,
we'll have plenty for everyone.
The whole family is waiting just for you.
Have you no shame?
Mom.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I was just going to check out
the birthday venue for you.
Oh, right.
Don't worry about my birthday venue.
My birthday venue is set at Fengtang.
Wanmei, go prepare the invitations after dinner.
I want to use Master Kista's wine
to entertain the guests.
And I'll showcase Valley Breeze's new wine
for everyone to taste.
Mom,
Fengtang is fully booked.
Besides,
Master Kista's wine can't be bought.
Did I say I was counting on you?
These things,
Luoluo has already taken care of them.
You just need to prepare the new products,
and make sure Valley Breeze doesn't lose face.
Mom,
with just this little brat?
How is that possible?
Why wouldn't it be possible?
Luoluo is an honored guest of Boss Yi.
This little matter
is hardly a challenge for her.
Luoluo, do you know
Yi Kai from Fengtang Club?
I worked in South Korea for a while.
I happened to run into Boss Yi
getting into a conflict with some locals.
Seeing he was a fellow countryman,
I gave him a hand.
My dear niece has pretty good luck.
Being able to latch onto someone like Boss Yi.
So, Luoluo,
you didn't get caught in the crossfire, did you?
No.
Don't worry, Grandma.
Since I was little,
my mom and I only had each other to rely on.
We met our fair share of malicious people.
If I didn't have a few tricks up my sleeve,
I wouldn't be alive today.
What a poor child.
Rest assured,
from now on, the Cheng family will back you up.
I'd like to see who
would still dare to bully you.
Come on,
let's eat.
Grandma,
have some of this.
Okay.
Using red roses to pay your respects...
In this entire cemetery,
you're the only one who'd do this.
These are Xiaowei's favorite flowers.
If I brought anything else,
she'd be upset.
Cheng An.
Don't underestimate a woman's jealousy.
Even if there's more to the competition,
the fact that she hurt Lin Wanmei
is undeniable.
Even if everyone else suspects her,
I don't.
I know she's not that kind of person.
I mentored Xiaowei myself.
I taught her how to make wine,
but I failed to teach her how to conduct herself.
She needed to keep a level head.
She was too eager for success,
and couldn't take defeat, so she hurt me.
For the sake of your happiness,
I'm willing to sign a letter of forgiveness.
I disagree!
Brother...
Cheng An,
your sister-in-law was lucky this time
to escape with her life.
Yes,
Ye Xiaowei has some talent,
but look at what she's done.
Just to win the championship,
she laced the wine with deadly arsenic!
As for those judges,
if they hadn't been treated in time,
our Valley Breeze Group
we'd face a manslaughter lawsuit by now.
Hello?
Cheng An,
I just landed in Seoul.
The prison informed me that Ms. Ye
committed suicide to escape punishment.
Cheng An, take my advice.
Let go of Ye Xiaowei, and spare yourself.
The succession battle is at a key stage.
Don't get distracted by someone who isn't worth it.
He Li.
I want to be alone for a while.
Disguise is what Cheng An does best.
Around the Cheng family and Valley Breeze,
he has never taken off his mask.
Tell me,
when you wear a mask for too long,
do you end up fooling even yourself?
Do you really not feel bad for him?
I heard that all these years, Cheng An
has been investigating the past incident.
Of course he'd investigate it.
Such a massive scandal,
how could he not take full advantage of it
and pin it on his rivals?
It seems that now,
the Cheng family is going to put on quite a show.
Of course.
All the pain I've suffered
will be repaid double.
She's asking for it.
Seeing her like this...
...I'm itching to hit her.
Scream!
She's asking for it.
Why isn't she fighting back?
Yeah, why isn't she fighting back?
Someone told me...
...to take good care of you in here.
What they want,
what they cherish,
I'll take it all away.
Oh, my dear girl.
You're finally here.
Where's the bag?
We need to return it quickly
before Madam finds out.
What happened to it?
I kept telling you
to be careful.
Be careful!
How could you...
What do we do now?
Will she make us pay for it?
Oh, you.
Stop idling around all day,
and hanging out with shady friends.
Find a good man and get married soon.
You're always making me worry.
Well, I want to marry Cheng An!
But you won't let me.
Don't even think about it.
Stay far away from the Cheng men.
Can't I even dream about it?
Auntie Ying.
This is your daughter, right?
She's so pretty.
Madam's bag got dirty.
I had Xiaoyu take it out to clean it.
Today
happens to be her birthday,
so the two of us
just chatted for a bit.
Since it's her birthday,
why doesn't she stay the night?
There's no need...
Yes, I'd love to!
I'll stay
and keep Mom company.
Auntie Ying,
we're all family.
It's only right she stays to keep you company.
Don't be so polite.
LV crocodile skin.
You can't buy this domestically.
Madam, I...
Do you like this bag?
Having been with Aunt for so many years,
Auntie Ying certainly has good taste.
You misunderstood, Madam.
There was a coffee stain on this bag.
I took it out to be cleaned.
This bag...
when Cheng An went to Italy,
Feng specifically asked him to buy it for me.
It really is a special gift.
You can have it.
I can't accept this.
Sir gave this to you.
It wouldn't be appropriate for me to take it.
Feng is gone.
This family has to look forward.
I can't dwell on his belongings forever.
Besides,
if Feng knew
how well Auntie Ying takes care of me,
he'd want to thank you too.
In that case,
I'll accept it.
I'll go back to work downstairs then.
If you need anything, Madam,
just call me.
Mm.
It's been dry lately,
Mom made Snow fungus and lily bulb soup
to soothe everyone's throats.
Sorry about that.
It's fine.
I can do it myself.
Pei Yu.
Where's mine?
You can serve yourself.
Auntie Ying.
What is this?
Playing favorites?
Come here.
Auntie Ying.
Is the Cheng house
a place just anyone can enter?
I asked Xiaoyu to stay.
Today is Xiaoyu's birthday.
I thought
she could have a meal with Auntie Ying.
How long have you been with the Chengs?
And you're already calling the shots?
Who knows what you'll do next.
Grandma.
Aunt.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think it through.
Sit down.
Pei Yu,
you
should stay with us a few more days
to keep Auntie Ying company.
Thank you, Old Madam Cheng.
Let's eat.
Here.
Mom saved this just for you.
Bird's nest.
You need to behave yourself
and steer clear of the Chengs.
Especially Cheng An.
Why?
He's the one Old Madam dislikes the most.
Any day now,
he could get kicked out of the company.
Aren't they all Old Madam's sons?
What do you know?
What about Cheng Yan?
Absolutely not!
He's Old Madam Cheng's absolute favorite.
Other mothers always hope their daughters
marry into wealthy families.
I want you to marry well too,
but not the Chengs.
Mom,
you're spoiling Auntie Ying too much.
How could you let her daughter stay here?
It's rare for them to reunite.
Even so, it's not right.
It's completely against the rules.
Rules are secondary.
My third son isn't getting any younger.
It's time he settled down.
I can tell Auntie Ying's daughter
quite likes him.
You know what?
A rose may seem arrogant.
Its thorns
hurt those who try to hurt it,
but also scare away those who love it.
But you know what?
If you look closely, you'll find
it's actually
a very gentle little flower.
So,
you like this little flower?
Alright then, now I know.
Know what?
I just know, don't worry about it.
Smell it, does it smell nice?
Madam.
You don't make a sound when you walk.
You scared me.
Is this how Auntie Ying educates her daughter?
Walking around half-dressed in this house.
What do you mean half-dressed?
If you ask me,
you're jealous of my youth and beauty.
You married a dead man,
and actually think you're a phoenix now.
Wait till I win over Cheng An.
We'll see how arrogant you can be then.
What kind of behavior is this?
Making such a racket late at night.
How improper.
It's so late.
Heading out to have fun?
No, Madam.
I can't sleep.
I'm just going for a walk.
A walk is good.
Out in the courtyard,
there are lots of roses.
The kind you girls like best.
Oh, right.
Today is your birthday.
I didn't have time to prepare anything.
Come here.
Mr. Cheng.
It's so late.
Drinking all alone?
Get out.
Mr. Cheng,
Care to try my wine?
I said, get out.
I was just worried you'd be lonely.
It's getting chilly tonight.
You're wearing so little.
Won't you catch a cold?